mdnhinc.com 2007-05-29

# MDNH Privacy Statement

### MDNH Privacy Statement

MDNH respects your privacy. Our purpose in collecting information from you is to help us provide you with better service, such as notifications about special offers and promotions. We will not willfully disclose any individually identifiable information about you to any third party without first receiving your permission, as explained in this privacy statement. Furthermore, we do not specifically target children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly collect, without parental consent, individually identifiable information from such children. 

We may request that an entity applying for an account with MDNH provide us with certain personal information (such as its name, email address, etc.) relevant to our provision of the various services offered on our site. We do not collect any personal information other than that which is specifically and knowingly provided to us. When we request information, we explain how it may be used and give you an opportunity to request that the information not be used for those purposes. We also give you an opportunity to opt out of future communications from us. 

Like most sites, for account management purposes, MDNH uses cookies. Cookies are data files stored on your computer that identify you as a unique user. Cookies enable us to track user trends, preferences and patterns to better understand our user base and to improve the quality of our service. Most browsers permit users to refuse cookies or to be notified before a cookie is accepted. You can visit our site without using cookies. 

The MDNH website contains links to other sites. Those sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. We are not responsible or liable for the privacy practices or content of such sites since we do not control them. 

MDNH may share non-personal and non-personally identifiable information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. However, we only divulge aggregate information, such as how often the average user visits our website. MDNH may partner with other parties in connection with the various services offered on our site, such as credit card processors or email delivery services. In such instances, we may share limited personal information that is necessary for the third-party to provide its services. These companies are prohibited from using this information for any other purpose. 

MDNH may also provide personal information when disclosure may be required by law (e.g., subpoenas, search warrants and court orders). We may also determine that such action is reasonably necessary to protect a party's rights, property, or well- being. This action may include exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud detection or protection, or in other situations involving suspicious or illegal activities. 

In the event of a transfer of ownership of MDNH, such as acquisition by or merger with another company, a user's personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. 

By using our site or services, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this privacy statement and consent to our Terms of Use. Additionally, if you are using any of our services, we may also collect and use information in accordance with such service's applicable Terms and Conditions. MDNH may decide to change this privacy statement from time to time. If and when we do, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

Feel free to contact us at any time with any questions you may have regarding our privacy statement. 

Effective December 18 2006. 

Back to top
